Hello and welcome friends today's
results of money ICICI Ambuja Cement
Supreme Furniture Shabd and Aarti Lyrics
ICICI Bank 60 according to that
looking good pimples are being created expenses are
flat they had to make provisioning the
team has had a positive impact on the low will only be
happy because positive
and Ambuja Cement runs on revenue
for a lot of people related to others
they have kept a good control on expenses
more videos so net profit is
positive subscribe subscribe button and
more than net profit has increased a lot in the
last some time subscribe so
these are the results of Supreme Plastics negative
revenue has fallen by 2017 percent running
share and net profit has
fallen by more than fifty percent so it's now good
friend recommendation is loop rice floor and keep fit
for long term
so friends these were today's short results will keep
bringing such results for you see you
in the next video